{
    "subject": "resource/January_07003:_Bell_Studies_for_the_Clock_of_the_Long_Now",
    "predicate": "ontology/artist",
    "object": "resource/Brian_Eno",
    "human_readable": "Brian Eno is the artist who created January 07003: Bell Studies for the Clock of the Long Now.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9443674087524414,
            "question": "Who created January 07003: Bell Studies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8923283219337463,
            "question": "What year was January 07003: Bell Studies created?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8734564185142517,
            "question": "What kind of art is January 07003: Bell Studies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8603721857070923,
            "question": "For what project was January 07003: Bell Studies created?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8013163805007935,
            "question": "What is the purpose of January 07003: Bell Studies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7437623143196106,
            "question": "Who is Brian Eno?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6951524615287781,
            "question": "Is Brian Eno a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5472025275230408,
            "question": "What is the Clock of the Long Now?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46197691559791565,
            "question": "What is the title of the work by Brian Eno?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42811819911003113,
            "question": "Can you describe the style of music Brian Eno is known for?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Brian Eno is the artist who created January 07003: Bell Studies for the Clock of the Long Now.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3147_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the title of the work by Brian Eno?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3147_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the Clock of the Long Now?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3147_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Brian Eno a musician?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3147_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3147_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3147_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3147_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3147_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3147_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3147_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3147_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3147_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3147_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3147_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The query is asking whether the information in the documents supports the triple \"Brian Eno is the artist who created January 07003: Bell Studies for the Clock of the Long Now.\".\n\nHere's the JSON response:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that Brian Eno created an album called \"January 07003\" and that it was inspired by a clock designed to operate for 10,000 years. Specifically, it says that Eno used the same algorithm for generating chime sequences in his album as was used in the Clock of the Long Now project. This suggests that Eno is indeed the artist who created January 07003: Bell Studies for the Clock of the Long Now."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"Experimental composer, artist, and producer Brian Eno has released a new album, \u201cJanuary 07003, Bell Studies for the Clock of the Long Now.\u201d\" This information supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}